[YOUNGJAE] [SHINYU] [←YOUNGJAE]
(YOUNGJAE) I think this is a good hiding spot
I wonder if the other guys are okay
(DOHOON) I think I'm really bad
at playing hide-and-seek
19 minutes and 30 seconds? Okay
[If he can't escape in 20 minutes
then he can't go out until the game ends]
[Phone alert] [JIHOON  →]
[One of your members is locked away]
I'll go and set DOHOON free right away
[← Prison] [JIHOON →]
(JIHOON) That's why I got a hiding spot
close to the prison
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
(HANJIN) It's so hot
Should we go out?
Go out?
I think it'll be scary again outside
-Should we go?
-Yeah, let's go
I'm so hot right now
(HANJIN) I'll open it
(HANJIN) It's so hot
What's going on?
Who is it?
[Sound of the seeker's footsteps]
Oh no
Let's go inside the big refrigerator
Come on
KYUNGMIN
(HANJIN) Is it the seeker?
I need the bathroom
[← The other members' numbers]
(DOHOON) I'll send them a text
instead of calling
I'll leave in 15 minutes
Luckily, I have a key that I found earlier
[YOUNGJAE  →]
(YOUNGJAE) I guess the seeker's not coming
here because I don't hear any footsteps
I don't hear any footsteps
[The seeker's footsteps] [JIHOON →]
The seeker's coming
[← JIHOON]
[The seeker's footsteps fade away]
Man, that was definitely the seeker for sure
I survived
[YOUNGJAE] [SHINYU] [Seeker]
[SHINYU →]
(SHINYU) Hey
Someone's coming
[← YOUNGJAE]
(YOUNGJAE) Please go!
(JIHOON) How do I save DOHOON?
(JIHOON) It's quiet out there now
[JIHOON doesn't know DOHOON has a key]
How did you know?
Wait, don't open it now
Why?
-I want to escape 15 minutes later
-(JIHOON) Why?
If you stay longer we don't know
what the survival rate will be like
I'll free DOHOON, thanks
Isn't it too early, though?
No, DOHOON, we should play harder
[After setting DOHOON free,
he goes back to his spot]
DOHOON's kicking up a fuss
even when I save him
Whoo!
[DOHOON escapes with JIHOON's key]
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
(DOHOON) I'll never be found in here
(DOHOON) Let me go in a bit deeper
(DOHOON) It's blocked over here. This is it!
If I hide here it's over
I've found my final destination
I'm so happy
[← YOUNGJAE] [The seeker goes to the machine room]
(YOUNGJAE) I'm so scared
[← YOUNGJAE]
[SHINYU →]
[← SHINYU]
[Found you, SHINYU!]
(SHINYU) I'm sorry
Oh man
I thought I'd never be found
[← YOUNGJAE]
(YOUNGJAE) I'll hang in there
like my life depends on it
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓] [Phone alert]
I think one of the members got caught
Come over here
Let's stay here for now
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN]
If I escape
I'll hide really well
Just one more chance
(DOHOON) I will never get caught here
[Phone alert]
[Hint for a key]
It's another hint for a key
I'm not going to look for it
I'm going to stay hidden
[Hint for a key]
I have an extra key right now
[JIHOON found one inside the manual forklift]
Going somewhere else is...
[Found the fourth key in the electric forklift]
It's better if I use this one me
[The seeker's footsteps]
He's coming
Turn off the lights
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN] [Seeker]
The key...
What is this?
[Finally spots the other members' numbers]
I can't believe I saw this now
I'm going crazy over here
JIHOON said he had a key
[Phone alert]
Be quiet
[Hey JIHOON, it's SHINYU.
I'm locked up. Please come and save me]
[JIHOON uses his key on SHINYU]
JIHOON?
JIHOON!
Oh no
[SHINYU → JIHOON]
I don't have a key now anymore
[SHINYU escapes the prison with JIHOON's key]
[The seeker's footsteps come closer]
Huh?
I'm here again
[SHINYU goes back into the machine room]
Oh my gosh
[A little wave]
(YOUNGJAE) I got a fright
Why am I here again?
I'm done for. What do I do?
(SHINYU) I feel so bad to JIHOON
I think this is the best place to hide
[← SHINYU]
(SHINYU) This is the best place
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
The seeker's here!
Sit down
[The seeker ↓]
Turn off the light!
[Sound of the seeker's footsteps]
(HANJIN) Oh no...
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN ↓]
Please, please!
Please
[Sound of the seeker's footsteps]
Is he gone?
(HANJIN) No, he's still here
[Found you HANJIN and KYUNGMIN!]
It's better to just get caught
We got caught
I lost my strength
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
[HANJIN and KYUNGMIN head to prison]
[JIHOON ↓]
Oh no, why did so many of them get caught?
Do I have to find more keys?
[Phone alert]
[Two members have been caught]
Oh no
(DOHOON) Shall I go?
(DOHOON) Since I've already found this spot
Who is that?
[DOHOON and HANJIN who each have a key]
Hold on
Shh!
[The seeker's footsteps]
[JIHOON ↓] [The seeker ↓]
Oh no
This is my opportunity
I have to go now
If I don't go now, we're in trouble
[Hint to the key]
A water bottle
I need to find a water bottle
I just need one key
[Sound of the seeker approaching]
Let me gain some time first
[Phone alert]
That made me jump!
We got a text
In a little while
[When there's 2,222 seconds left,
the seeker will disappear for a while]
you will have four minutes
to really hide yourselves
[After four minutes, there will be two seekers
so hide even better]
How many seconds are left?
The time's over there
I see it now
DOHOON, should we go out now?
[← DOHOON]
The seeker's in front over there
[The seeker disappears for a while]
[TWS has four minutes of freedom]
Save me!
[HANJIN escapes from prison]
I'll set him free
[KYUNGMIN escapes from prison with DOHOON's key]
It's four minutes starting now, right?
Having two seekers is horrifying
[JIHOON →]
Hey! Anyone with a key?
I don't! That's why I'm looking for it
[Hint for the key]
We need to find a blue garbage can
There's a blue garbage can here
but there're no keys
(JIHOON) It'd have been nice if it was here
but unfortunately it's not here
A blue garbage can
[← SHINYU]
I'll never get caught
[SHINYU stays hidden]
[YOUNGJAE also stays hidden]
[He's even blocked out the light]
But we really need a key
[Lost a key in the seeker box]
[TWS has already used up all four keys]
We have to find a key
I don't have time to walk around
I have to run
They say it's right under your nose
but I really can't see it
A blue trash can
Is it this one?
[HANJIN finds the fifth key in the movable trash can]
[An alert that the seekers are reappearing]
Oh no, it's starting
Ready or not
here I come
[HANJIN is breathing hard]
Ready or not
I couldn't find the key
here I come
(DOHOON) I'm going back
to my hiding spot from earlier
JIHOON, let's hide together
Hide somewhere close to me
I'm so scared
[JIHOON is making a double-layered shield]
[← KYUNGMIN] [KYUNGMIN pacing alone]
[Hides between two boxes]
Ready or not
here come two seekers
Are you all hiding?
Here we come
(DOHOON) I'll never get caught here
[DOHOON]
(DOHOON) Wow, this is literally
the best hiding spot
(DOHOON) Nobody can find me here
I will never get caught here
(DOHOON) Nobody can come in here
[← SHINYU] [YOUNGJAE] [SHINYU]
(SHINYU) I won't be found here for sure!
I mean honestly
there's nothing to do it
I just have to hide where nobody can find me
They will never find me
[Laughs]
[HANJIN ↓] [HANJIN]
(HANJIN) This is so hard
[The seeker's footsteps come closer]
They're here
[HANJIN] [Seeker]
[The seeker searches for the members
even harder than before]
It's so scary being here alone
[The seeker searches every corner
of the warehouse]
[The seeker and HANJIN get further apart]
I didn't manage to find the key in the end
[JIHOON doesn't know HANJIN has found it]
I'm sorry guys
I've wrapped myself up really tight
As you can see from the front
[JIHOON ↓]
(JIHOON) I'm going to survive no matter what
[JIHOON and KYUNGMIN] [KYUNGMIN←]
(KYUNGMIN) I'm hiding right now
but there are now two seekers
and we haven't found the key
[The seeker's footsteps draw closer]
They're coming
[Another seeker appears]
[← JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN →]
[Lights out]
Please don't come over here
[← KYUNGMIN] [← JIHOON]
[KYUNGMIN's CAM]
[Phone rings]
What the...
[← KYUNGMIN] [← JIHOON]
[The seeker's tracking the sound]
[JIHOON's breathing]
[KYUNGMIN's CAM] [The seeker →]
[I found you KYUNGMIN!]
Let's go
We don't even have a key
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
Who called me!
Let me call them
[DOHOON was the one who called JIHOON]
Did you find the key?
No I didn't
Where are you hiding?
I was hiding close to KYUNGMIN
but KYUNGMIN got caught
(DOHOON) He got caught? Oh no...
He called me over nothing
[KYUNGMIN got caught instead of JIHOON
whose phone rang]
[← SHINYU] [Phone vibrates]
Hello?
SHINYU, where are you?
I'm somewhere nobody can find me
-Are you hiding?
-(SHINYU) Yeah
-Did you find the key?
-(SHINYU) No
(SHINYU) Where are you?
(KYUNGMIN) In prison
-(SHINYU) In prison?
-(KYUNGMIN) Yeah
(SHINYU) Okay, I'll win this for us
-You're going to win this?
-(SHINYU) Yeah
-Okay SHINYU, but you can't set me free?
-Yeah
-Okay
[Laughs]
Everyone's hiding
[HANJIN↓]
(HANJIN) Well
in October, for our fourth mini album
when we do our comeback
we'd be grateful for all your love
[The seeker appears while HANJIN is promoting]
There are lots of amazing songs
[The seeker's footsteps are coming closer]
in the album
so please give it a listen
[The seeker's footsteps]
[Gulping sound]
[← HANJIN] [← Seeker]
[← HANJIN] [The seeker goes closer to HANJIN]
[The seeker walks past]
[and the footsteps fade away]
[But just then]
[Phone vibrates]
[The seeker heads toward the sound]
(HANJIN) Hold on please
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
(HANJIN) I just got a call from someone
(SHINYU) How much time is left?
They'll never find me here
[The seeker appears right away]
[← YOUNGJAE] [SHINYU →]
(SHINYU) He's coming
[The seeker's coming closer and closer]
[Found you YOUNGJAE!]
I got caught
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
(YOUNGJAE) Oh man...
But did you find the key?
I'll escape now
-Don't leave
-Why?
-There are three of us still out there
-Yeah
There are still three left
but if you...
Guys, I got caught...
We just need half of us to survive
Won't we all be able to survive if I go out?
(KYUNGMIN) No, I mean
(KYUNGMIN) HANJIN, you need to escape
when we're nearly finished to win
Really?
-Fifty percent of us
-We need at least three to succeed
Right now, three of us are
hiding in really good spots
[JIHOON ↓]
(JIHOON) Logically, right now
even if I did have the key
I can't go to the prison
It's a challenge after a challenge.
Finding the key is difficult
and taking the key
and going to the prison is difficult too
[TWS's survival rate is 50% and one key left]
This is fine
It's been a long time being able to
spend time like this
[Phone alert]
[There are 444 seconds left]
Even faster than the seekers
are their shadows, who're on the move now
If you get caught by a shadow, there'll be
[a siren sound so don't ever get caught]
They'll never find me here
[← JIHOON]
(JIHOON) Shadows...
are apparently coming
I need to stay silent
Will TWS be able to get the presents for 42?
[At 444 seconds, something comes out]
[The shadows begin to move]
What's going on?
[← JIHOON]
[Enters the area where JIHOON's hiding]
[← JIHOON] [Are the shadows
heading toward him?]
They're coming
[JIHOON →]
[Searches carefully among the boxes]
[but fails to find JIHOON and leaves]
I nearly almost got caught
I can't lift my head
[JIHOON sighs]
[←SHINYU]
What's going on!
[SHINYU →] [A shadow enters
the machine room]
[The shadow draws closer]
[Shadow's CAM]
[← SHINYU] [← Shadow]
[Goes closer to SHINYU]
[Shadow's CAM] [SHINYU →]
[The shadow doesn't see SHINYU in the dark]
(SHINYU) What did I tell you?
(SHINYU) I'm not weak
[Alert that 20 minutes are up]
(YOUNGJAE) I think KYUNGMIN's out
(HANJIN) KYUNGMIN's out now
[KYUNGMIN can escape now that 20 minutes are up]
[SHINYU] [DOHOON] [YOUNGJAE] [HANJIN]
[JIHOON] [KYUNGMIN]
Gatekeeper, can you come here?
Come slowly, please!
Hold on
Can I have a second to think about it?
[There are 200 seconds left]
[Sound of the shadows] [← DOHOON]
They're here
[Shadow's CAM]
[Lights out]
Please...
[Shadow's CAM] [Doesn't spot DOHOON in the dark]
[The shadow goes away]
I have one minute left
[Only one minute left]
[← JIHOON] [The shadows are moving faster]
(JIHOON) Are they back?
The're back again?
[The seekers are getting faster now]
There's 30 seconds left
Getting ready to escape
Can you come over here please?
[Only ten seconds left]
[HANJIN escapes from prison]
[Hide-and-seek ends]
I give up, where are you?
It's over
(SHINYU) Wait, is it over?
Is it over?
[Phone alert]
It's over now
[The hide-and-seek game is over now.
Come to the prison to check the survival rate]
[TWS wins with a final survival rate of 66.7%]
-Did you survive?
-Yeah, I came out with 10 seconds left
[All the survivors come to the prison]
I didn't see the seeker even once
-Where were you?
-Where were you hiding?
Did you see where I was hiding?
-(KYUNGMIN) Is that where you were?
-Yeah
-(KYUNGMIN) Were you there the whole time?
I was in the best hiding spot over
I found a spot where there were no cameras
Where? There's a spot like that?
I was hiding somewhere
they’d never find me too
[Phone alert]
[Hide-and-seek is over and survival rate is over 50%]
so 42 gets snack treats
I was literally
holding my breath so I could get 42 presents!
-I really did my best
-For real
[The seeker's scream]
Don't you dare look back!